

Altes Idriz

Junior JavaScript Developer

A web developer specializing in JavaScript and React. With two years as a technical manager and six years as a sales manager, I bring a unique blend of technical expertise and business acumen. Currently enhancing my skills through ongoing web development studies, I am eager to contribute my proficiency and dedication to innovative projects.

■altes.fidail@gmail.com

Q 0899 95 98 36

Sofia Bulgaria

in linkedin.com/in/altes.idriz

Ohttps://github.com/LetRookie



EDUCATION

Full-Stack Web Developer

Software University

09/2021 - Present Professional Modules

JavaScript Advanced

A course for in-depth knowledge of the JavaScript language. Working with the DOM tree, manipulations on it, and handling events. Functional and Object-Oriented Programming (OOP) approaches in JavaScript, inheritance, object composition, prototype chains and etc.

JavaScript Applications

HTTP requests, REST services, Backend as a Service (BaaS), asynchronous code (Promises, use of async/await), templating, and routing. Creating a Single Page Application.

HTML and CSS

"Knowledge of HTML5 and CSS3 for web development, web browsers, tools for HTML/CSS/DOM development, and practical skills in using the language for describing web content (HTML) and the language for styling web content (CSS).

JavaScript Back-End

"The development of server-side JavaScript applications on the Node.js platform, using Express.js as a framework. Server-client architecture and data-driven web applications with Node.js, Express.js, and MongoDB. Working with MongoDB-Mongoose library. Building REST APIs using Express.js and MongoDB."

ReactJS

"Developing Single Page Applications using ReactJS technology. Writing with JSX syntax, handling requests and Promises,routing, form validation,styling components using techniques like CSS Modules and Styled Components. React Hooks, Context API.Unit testing with JEST."

Software Technologies and Design

PU Plovdiv

09/2019 - Present

Transport Engineering

UACEG Sofia

09/2008 - 07/2015



WORK EXPERIENCE

Technical Manager/Road Constructions

Global Transport Engineering

03/2015 - 01/2016

Technical Manager in Civil Constructions

ELER Kaldera

04/2019 - 02/2020

Sales Manager

REM Engineering 08

02/2016 - Present



TECHNICAL SKILLS

Programming Languages

Js Java Script

₹ css3

👙 Java

© C#

HTML5

Frameworks

React

⊖X ExpressJS

NodeJS

Databases

MongoDB
 MongoDB

Firebase
PostreSQL

Tools

Visual Studio Code

Web Storm

⋈ Visual Studio

InteliJ IDEA



SOFT SKILLS

Attention to detail

Communication Analysis

Teamwork & cooperation Analysis



PERSONAL PROJECTS

Booking Page @

Full stack web application, written in JavaScript with React, Express, MongoDB, JWT and MVC pattern

Car Offer Page @

Full stack web application, written in JavaScript with React, Express, MongoDB and MVC pattern



LANGUAGES

Bulgarian

Native

English

Turkish

Nativ